A Guide to the Trudy Norfleet Collection, 1956-1981
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Trudy Norfleet Collection, 1956-1981
Library of Virginia
39367
0.45 cubic feet.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Trudy Norfleet of Richmond, Virginia, in March 2002.
Biographical Information
Trudy Norfleet was a long-time employee of the Virginia Governor's Office.
Scope and Content
Collection, 1956-1981, of Trudy Norfleet, who served in the Virginia Governor's Office for many years. Includes correspondence, programs, itineraries, photographs, clippings, and memorabilia concerning events during the terms of Thomas B. Stanley and John Dalton and the two terms of Mills E. Godwin, Jr. Notable contents include a copy of the 1966 inaugural prayer, an inauguration program for Mills E. Godwin, Jr., 1966, and individual photographs of Godwin and his wife Katherine.
Arrangement
Arranged into three series: I. Thomas B. Stanley, 1956; II. Mills E. Godwin, Jr., 1965-1976; III. John Dalton, 1977-1981.
Contents List
- Thomas B. Stanley, 1956, 0.01 cubic feet. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Contains a Gubernatorial Commemmorative Tour of Europe booklet, 1956.
- Mills E. Godwin, Jr. 1965-1976, 0.43 cubic feet. (Box 1, Folders 2-16)
  Includes correspondence, programs, itineraries, photographs, clippings, and memorabilia concerning events during the two terms of Mills E. Godwin, Jr. Contains an inauguration program for 1966 and photographs of Godwin and his wife Katherine.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically.
  - Bicentennial program and dinner itinerary, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Campaign clippings, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - European trip booklets and itineraries, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - European trip correspondence, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - European trip newspaper clippings, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Mansion tours report, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly Joint Commemmorative Session programs and itineraries, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Governors' Conference press statements, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Inaugural prayer, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Inauguration program, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Memorabilia, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous programs, 1976, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Promotional map of Norfolk, 1974 (Map-case 4/G/8, Drawer 3, Folder 1)
  - Southern Governors' Conference booklets and itineraries, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- John Dalton, 1977-1981, 0.01 cubic feet. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Consists of correspondence, 1977-1981, including an inaugural ball invitation, 1977, and a letter, 3 April 1981, from M. Caldwell Butler, United States Representative from the 6th District of Virginia.
  Arranged chronologically within the folder.